(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(The trotters are perfectly boiled by now.)
(The first round of boiling is complete.)
(She's about to take the trotters out of the water.)
(Pulled out through clouds of hot steam)
(It's plump and bouncy.)
Gosh, it's hot.
(Once the trotters are out of the water,)
(it'll be boiled again with aromatic spices.)
I need to throw it away.
(Jung Ah is about to wash the pot...)
(for the second round of boiling.)
Isn't it too heavy?
(Lifting easily)
- Move out of the way.
- Will you throw it away here?
Move out of the way.
(What is that sound?)
- What's the matter?
- What is it?
What's wrong, Sun Young?
Oh, no. There's a snake!
(A snake?)
- Where is it?
- My goodness.
There's a snake.
Why are you going in there?
(The production crew is also startled by news of a snake.)
(Murmuring)
My goodness.
- Where is the snake?
- There's a snake.
Where is it?
(Where's the snake?)
Why are you going in there?
Where is it?
- It's dangerous. Don't go in.
- Don't go.
- Hey.
- You Seok.
Don't go there, You Seok.
What is he doing?
My goodness. You Seok.
You Seok, come back here.
You can't use that.
No way. What are you doing?
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
What happened?
(Serious)
Guys, go and take a look.
He's going in to catch it.
But...
(Serious)
(Screaming)
(Everyone is extremely tense.)
Don't go in there, You Seok!
Are you out of your mind?
Goodness.
(Did he catch the snake with his hand?)
(And he runs outside.)
It's a snake.
(The snake remains completely still.)
Are you out of your mind?
It's a snake.
(Laughing)
- My goodness.
- You startled me.
You really startled me.
(Actually, it was just a toy snake.)
(Laughing)
(The four siblings' prank...)
(on the production crew was a huge success.)
I did all that just for this.
(Her talent put to excess use)
Sae Hee.
(Terrified even while knowing that it's fake)
I went all out while running around barefoot.
(On the cement floor)
(Even over the gravel)
(Sun Young, the barefoot actress...)
(ran around without shoes to give it her all.)
Sun Young is such an amazing actress.
My feet are killing me.
I know. She went through it barefoot.
(Sun Young's barefoot dedication stole the show.)
- Did you bring it from Seoul?
- Of course.
We came up with this...
the moment we got taken away on the boat.
We couldn't be the only ones getting pranked.
We planned this for a month.
(A month ago)
(Why?)
(What's going on here?)
(What's going on?)
(A mental breakdown)
(The humiliating kidnapping they endured on the first day)
(You Seok, someday...)
(we have to get our revenge.)
(We definitely have to get them back.)
(And so began the siblings' secret scheme.)
(How will we fool the production staff?)
(Then the toy snake idea came up.)
(Shall I buy a toy snake?)
(The snake idea was chosen with enthusiastic approval.)
How about this?
(A few days earlier, somewhere in Seoul)
What's our final move?
Throwing the snake?
Because he got so sweaty,
he goes inside to change his shirt.
Then he leaves the snake there.
(Before making dinner)
(Rummaging around)
(You Seok secretly took out the toy snake...)
(that he brought in advance.)
(Walking casually)
(I am...)
(going in now.)
(Got it)
I'm going to the bathroom.
(Coming back out with empty hands)
I'm going to use the bathroom.
Okay.
Jung Ah, I'll go and use the bathroom.
Of course.
(Unable to hide his excitement at the signal to begin)
(Screaming)
(Led by Sun Young,)
(the four siblings began their acting tour de force.)
(Sending the production staff into complete panic)
(The production staff fell for it completely.)
When I went inside to catch the snake,
I expected someone to follow me.
- No one went after him.
- No one.
I went to catch the snake.
We expected the staff to come inside.
(I was on my way over with a shovel.)
I got so caught up in the moment that I strained my neck.
(The production staff says, "We won't forget.")
You Seok kept laughing inside because no one could see him.
- We're done cooking.
- Right.
- Jung Ah has to make trotters.
- Yes.
Today, I'm determined to make trotters with zero unpleasant smell.
(Mission: Make trotters without the smell)
(What's Chef Yum's secret to getting rid of that pork smell?)
(Scrubbing)
(Rinsing the boiled trotters)
(If you rinse the trotters after the first boil, you can remove...)
(the impurities that cause the unpleasant smell...)
(and give it a cleaner flavour.)
(I won't miss even the tiniest bit of impurities.)
(Once the trotters are thoroughly cleaned,)
(add soy sauce to the boiling water.)
(Then add dark soy sauce to deepen the colour.)
(Making a base to bring out the colour and flavour of trotters)
(Adding trotters)
(Two pieces)
(Three pieces)
(trotters keeps going in generously.)
(It's finally over after eight pieces.)
We have to add two eggs.
(Shall I get rid of the porky smell again?)
Eggs?
(Secret 1 for removing the smell: Soju)
I have to get rid of the smell.
Getting rid of the smell is the most important.
(Bad smell, go away!)
(Secret 2 for removing the smell: Bay leaves)
(Dried chilli peppers, green onions, pears, onions)
(Secret 3 for removing the smell: Adding various ingredients)
(Cinnamon sticks are good for getting rid of unwanted odours.)
(Whole garlic cloves peeled by Sun Young)
(We can't forget the whole black peppercorns.)
(Adding doenjang from a container)
Let's see. Did I add everything?
I'll add some sugar.
(Adding sugar to tenderize the meat and finish it)
(All you have to do is let the trotters simmer away.)
Let it boil nice and hard.
I added all kinds of things to get rid of the smell.
(You Seok who is in charge of seasoned dried radish)
You Seok, what are you making?
- Seasoned dried radish?
- After seasoning dried radish...
What's this?
Dried chilli pepper leaves.
- For seasoned dried radish?
- Yes.
These are good with dried radish.
(You Seok confidently pulls out the dried chilli pepper leaves.)
Have you made it before?
- You just try everything.
- So you haven't.
(Laughing)
There's a first time for everything.
(It's his first time making seasoned dried radish.)
You learn by doing.
(It's not that complicated. You just wing it.)
(Tossing dried chilli pepper leaves into the boiling water)
Thirty seconds.
One, two...
I'll make the seasoning for the dried radish.
You just do it by feel.
You throw in this and that to make it.
(Sprinkling in chilli powder)
Where's the thick soy sauce? Is the yangjo soy sauce better?
Where's the yangjo soy sauce?
Should I just add thick soy sauce?
Should I add yangjo soy sauce?
(I don't know anything about recipes.)
Should I add thick soy sauce?
(Casually pouring in thick soy sauce)
(Tuna fish sauce, sand lance sauce, oligosaccharide)
(Also adding garlic and sugar)
(And ginger juice to remove odours and add a rich flavour)
(He makes the seasoning on the spot without hesitation.)
(Don't I do it well without recipes?)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
Can you taste it?
- What is it?
- Seasoning for the dried radish.
Dried radish?
(Asking Chef Yum for confirmation now that he's made it)
(Analysing the taste)
It's good, but it's a little too salty.
- Is it? But I have to mix them.
- Of course.
Don't add all the seasoning. Add it as you go.
(Squeeze the dried radish that has been soaking in cooking wine)
(Rinse the boiled dried chilli pepper leaves)
(Bring the dried radish and dried chilli pepper leaves together)
(Adding the seasoning)
(All he has to do is mix them up.)
(Massaging gently)
(The dried radish is dressed in a beautiful red sauce.)
Gosh, that looks good. You should add sesame seeds...
- Do you want to try it?
- and sesame oil.
- Did you already add sesame oil?
- No, not yet.
(Try it first.)
(Analysing the taste)
It's good.
- Is it not too bland?
- No.
You need to add sesame oil and sesame seeds.
I'll pour some sesame oil for you.
(Under the supervisor's direction)
Please pour it in.
(Adding sesame oil and sesame seeds)
(Massaging it gently one more time)
(Taking a bite to taste)
(One more bite to see if it tastes good)
You Seok, did you make it?
(You Seok's first seasoned dried radish is ready.)
When did he make it so fast?
(Sun Young tastes it too.)
You Seok, it's delicious.
Does it taste okay?
(Glancing?)
Can you make it sweeter?
- Shall I add some sugar?
- Right?
- You can make it a little sweeter.
- I can add sugar...
- Otherwise, it tastes good.
- or oligosaccharide.
Really? Make it sweeter?
(The mild flavour lover)
(Intimidated)
- Did you see her eyes just now?
- To your taste...
- I did.
(Actually, I saw them.)
This is enough, Jung Ah. The sweetness is perfect like this.
(She intimidates her with a single look.)
Should I chop the garlic scapes?
- Cut them the way you know.
- Okay.
Take them with you. I'm done with them.
Yes. Everybody, go.
It's hard to find garlic scapes grown in Korea.
(So begins another Dae Jang Geum-style chopping time.)
(Chop)
(The garlic scapes are sliced in the hands of a chopping master.)
Where I used to live...
in the US, we didn't eat garlic scapes.
I really wanted to eat them when I came back to Korea.
(Her Jennica character returns.)
It's my first time cooking with harvested garlic scapes.
- Do you want me to braid your hair?
- It's okay.
- No?
- No. Just leave it.
Let it be free.
(Jennica's hair, the symbol of freedom)
Yoon Seo, are you a member...
- of S.O.S?
- I was a member of S.O.S.
I debuted a while ago,
but I spent a long time struggling as an unknown.
I've been working part-time jobs...
- before starting to study acting.
- Really?
It wasn't easy trying to make it.
Is there anything you've acted in Korea that we can watch?
I'm good at acting scared of snakes.
- That kind of acting?
- Yes.
Gosh, that's so amazing.
(Jennica can also do it with confidence.)
- I act in the US.
- In the US?
- I'm learning from Matt Damon.
- What?
You're learning from Matt Damon?
- It's a secret.
- It's a secret?
- After training for 1 more month, - For 1 more month?
- I'll come to Korea.
- Why Korea?
- What?
- Why will you come to Korea?
- In Korea...
Oh, I see.
I'm more comfortable speaking...
- American English than Korean.
- I can understand.
Because...
(Jennica expands her universe while speaking nonsense.)
(Meanwhile, Chef Yum can't step away from the trotters.)
The fire keeps dying down.
(The heat is too weak, and the pot won't boil.)
This is a problem.
(The more worried she gets, the more firewood she throws in.)
(Instead of a bigger fire, all she gets is a cloud of smoke.)
I'll take care of the fire.
(It is my turn to step in again?)
(Dropping like it's no big deal)
(Shall I get started?)
I put in too much firewood at once, didn't I?
There's no room for air, so the fire dies down.
The flame needs to rise.
(Don't worry, Jung Ah!)
It'll come back to life in no time.
(He carefully controls the fire.)
(The man of fire, Kang You Seok)
(With just one touch, the flames roar back to life.)
- Is this fire strong enough?
- Yes.
(This is perfect.)
- My gosh.
- It's starting to boil.
(Thanks to him, the trotter sauce starts boiling.)
You Seok, is there anything that you can't do?
What I can't do?
(I'm Kang You Seok. What can't I do?)
(I can't put out a fire.)
(But I can set your heart on fire.)
(Reality hits him.)
Wait, let me do it again. I won't laugh.
(Getting absorbed again)
(I'm You James Dean.)
(Here we go.)
What are you doing?
(Yoon Seo, do you still see me as Kang You Seok?)
(I'm You James Dean.)
(Flustered)
(A world of their own)
(There's one more shot left.)
Was that okay? We got it.
(Thanks to the man of fire, You Seok)
Cook up nice and delicious.
- Shall I cover it with a lid?
- No.
- The odour has to evaporate.
- The odour has to go away?
Yes.
I have a good feeling about tonight's trotters.
(Shall I start making stir-fried garlic scapes with dried shrimp?)
(Adding dried shrimp first)
About this much.
(Stir-fry the dried shrimp without oil to get rid of the fishy smell.)
(Once they're toasted, set them aside.)
(Now, add some oil to the pan.)
(Toss in the garlic scapes Jennica chopped.)
(Stir-fry the garlic scapes until they're nicely cooked.)
(Now, add the dried shrimp that was set aside.)
(Stir-fry again)
(Tasting the garlic scape)
The smell.
The garlic scapes are very delicious.
(It's perfect with sharp, garlic aroma and flavour.)
By the way,
to stir-fried garlic scapes...
(A secret weapon in Jung Ah's dish)
It's a secret weapon.
It's a must-have in your fridge.
It's very useful when making side dishes.
(Drizzling a lot of sauce)
It's an umami-packed base...
that brings out the flavours of the ingredients.
It goes well with anything.
(An instant umami boost)
- You have to add plenty.
- To make it nice and nutty.
(Finishing off with sesame seeds for extra nuttiness)
It looks so delicious.
It's hot.
(Yoon Seo tastes it first.)
(Humming)
(Give me some too.)
It's so good.
It's very flavourful.
- It's better when it cools down.
- The flavour is insane.
It's very tasty.
We just need to finish cooking the trotters.
Please be delicious.
I bet it will be amazing.
(How do the trotters look after 50 minutes of cooking?)
They're almost done.
It's tasty when the seasoning really soaks in.
(A little more time for the sauce to seep into the trotters)
(You Seok gives the fire one last boost with more firewood.)
Gazing at the fire.
- Do you want to watch the fire?
- Yes.
- The firewood smells good.
- Nothing beats watching a fire.
(A fire so mesmerizing that you can't help but stare)
(Meanwhile, Jung Ah is mesmerized by the trotters.)
(This time, she stares at Jung Ah.)
Jung Ah, seriously...
What?
Jung Ah, you look so...
Your chef look today is seriously amazing.
- She's a total femme fatale.
- You look incredible.
- The chef is very hot. So pretty.
- Your looks...
Seriously.
Don't we look so funny?
- Right now...
- We're used to it by now.
(You James Dean who became the man of fire)
(The chefs may look somewhat shocking.)
(But the trotters...)
Please be delicious.
It will be delicious.
(It looks absolutely insane.)
There's no way it tastes bad.
(The trotters turned golden brown.)
Yoon Seo, please plate the food beautifully.
Whatever.
(With Yoon Seo's touch, the makguksu looks perfect.)
- I just have to cut it.
- It's all done.
Please...
(It's time to slice the trotters and bring it to the table.)
(Gloves for the trotters are ready.)
It's time for surgery.
This is how you do it.
- Like this?
- Yes.
(Preparing to slice the trotters with deadly seriousness)
Please save it.
- Seriously.
- Please...
- Please save it.
Please be delicious.
(The trotters look perfectly cooked from the outside.)
(Scalpel in hand, the trotters go onto the operating table.)
(A tense moment)
(Will the trotters be cooked perfectly?)
(Juicy, tender meat bursting with moisture)
It looks insane.
(Bouncy)
Please.
It looks good.
(It looks perfectly cooked.)
Can you taste it?
- Shall I taste it?
- Yes.
- I'll judge it very objectively.
- Okay.
I feel nervous. Have a piece.
(Nervous)
(trotters made by Jung Ah)
(Jung Ah's goal is trotters without any unpleasant smell.)
Is it too bland?
(Did she successfully remove the unpleasant smell?)
(After savouring it for a long time,)
(he shows a mysterious smile.)
- Seriously.
- It looks good.
Is it seriously good?
It made me smile as soon as I ate it.
- It looks good.
- It's very good.
- Do you want some?
- Try it.
First of all...
(Surprised by the rich flavour that hits the moment you eat it)
- Jung Ah.
- Is it seasoned...
When you eat it with your eyes closed, it's not trotters.
It melts in your mouth.
Is it seasoned...
- It's completely seasoned.
- Is it?
- Definitely.
- You don't need any sauce?
I thought you added some medicinal herbs.
Doesn't it taste like medicinal herbs?
- Jung Ah.
- You don't need any sauce with it.
Hold on.
There's absolutely no porky smell.
I'm serious.
- It has a rich flavour.
- The flavour is excellent.
The flavour is excellent.
(Making trotters without smell is a huge success.)
(She finally smiles after hearing that there's no smell.)
Even Americans can eat this.
We got rid of the smell completely.
- Even Americans?
- It's okay for Americans too.
Can I try?
Of course.
(Trying the trotters)
- Jung Ah, it's so delicious.
- Really? It doesn't smell bad?
It's very chewy.
How do you say "chewy" in English?
Oh, my gosh.
It's just like jelly. Oh, my gosh.
It turned out well.
It really turned out well.
I'll cut it for you.
- Gosh, it's good.
- Jung Ah.
You have to try it right now.
- All together.
- I'll give you some.
I'll give it to you.
(Good food is best when you share it.)
Give it to them right away when I cut it.
(Everyone, open up.)
You have to eat it right now.
- It's really good.
- Isn't it?
- It's like something you buy.
- Who hasn't tried it yet?
Gosh, try some.
I'm not just saying this. It's seriously delicious.
Jung Ah, it's a piece of art.
- Really?
- Yes.
It'll taste even better with this garlic sauce.
I'll sprinkle the garlic sauce over it.
Gosh, this is...
(A drizzle of garlic sauce as the finishing touch)
If you sold this, you'd make a fortune.
It tastes insanely good.
(The ultimate garlic trotters are complete.)
(Yoon Seo finishes the makguksu with the sauce she made.)
It looks delicious.
(Spicy and tangy makguksu made by the art major)
This is no joke. I'm so good at this.
(A perfect match for trotters)
Gosh, this is good.
(You Seok's seasoned dried radish)
(Stir-fried garlic scapes with dried shrimp as a side dish)
(And pickled onions You Seok made back in Seoul)
How does Jung Ah cook everything so well?
(A generous trotters feast is finally spread across the table.)
All right, let's eat now.
- Let's eat.
Okay. Mix them in there.
(The makguksu goes into a large mixing bowl.)
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Should we serve on individual plates?
(The makguksu chef gives it a hands-on mixing service.)
(The noodles are tossed in a sweet and tangy red sauce.)
I can tell from the smell that it's delicious.
It's made by Yoon Seo.
(A volunteer taste tester appears.)
How will her makguksu taste?
(It's time for the taste test, and the tension kicks in.)
I'm so scared.
(The nerve-racking moment of the first bite)
It's good.
- Yoon Seo, it's delicious.
- Is it?
Yoon Seo.
(You Seok gives garlic trotters to Yoon Seo.)
(Humming)
Seriously...
(You Seok also tries some garlic trotters.)
(One bite in, and the exclamations begin.)
The trotters are incredible.
(Over the perfectly cooked, chewy and bouncy trotters)
I'm not kidding.
The garlic sauce has a nice kick to it.
(The spicy garlic sauce cuts right through the richness.)
(Jung Ah piles on a generous amount of garlic sauce.)
- It has a kick to it.
- Yes.
Seosan is reclaimed farmland,
so the garlic grows...
(The honorary ambassador of Seosan garlic appears suddenly.)
It grows really well there.
It's even better than takeout.
(Seasonal garlic makes the trotters even more delicious.)
It's ready now.
You're supposed to wrap trotters with makguksu, right?
trotters is always served with tray noodles.
(Trotters and makguksu make the perfect match.)
(Just like this)
(Delicious plus delicious equals more delicious.)
(Jung Ah takes a bite of trotters first.)
(She cleanses the palate with spicy makguksu.)
(Slurping in)
(The spicy, tangy sauce cuts through the richness of trotters.)
(You Seok piles up vegetables on the noodles.)
(Crunch)
(The vegetables leave the mouth feeling fresh and light.)
(The makguksu chef also takes a bite.)
The sauce tasted salty on its own,
but it works perfectly when everything is mixed.
It's good.
- You can make it now, right?
- Yes.
- You can make it.
- I can make it tastier.
It'd be good even if it were spicier.
(It's the best.)
(After a bite of chewy trotters)
(She tries it with You Seok's dried radish this time.)
Dried radish is good too.
(It passes the big sister's test.)
(Sun Young grabs a piece of lettuce to make a wrap.)
(trotters)
(Ssamjang)
(Dried radish)
It's ready now.
- You Seok's dish is delicious.
- Yes.
- It tastes good in a wrap.
- Auntie.
Do you want to bring some to the US?
- In the US, - Gosh, sorry.
you can't find things like this.
Will you miss it in the US?
Yes.
(A taste that she'll miss in the US)
(A combination of a spicy and sweet sauce and a chewy texture)
(Good food is irresistible.)
Gosh, sorry.
(Trotters and dried radish are meant to be eaten together.)
The dried radish.
- Isn't it good?
- Yes.
- It tastes good.
The dried radish is good too.
(Whoever made it, it's really good.)
(Thanks to the dishes made by the youngest siblings,)
(tonight's dinner has become even richer.)
The trotters are really amazing.
The eggs are perfectly boiled, too.
- They're delicious.
- Yoon Seo did a good job.
(Our youngest members can do it all.)
Jung Ah, for simple dishes like these...
Let's cook together.
- These two can make them.
- We can divide up the menu.
These two can handle them.
I'll prep the ingredients really quickly.
- That sounds good.
- They're good at making sauces too.
Yes, they're both very good.
I'll get better at cooking here.
- Do you want them together?
- It's so good.
(A bite of rice, and a bite of garlic scapes)
It's delicious.
(Three bites of garlic scapes)
I love...
garlic scapes.
(The piquant taste and umami make it the perfect side dish for rice.)
It's so good.
(As she enjoys that satisfying crunch,)
(the rice naturally follows.)
(Jung Ah is also hooked on seasonal stir-fried garlic scapes.)
(With the lingering umami filling their mouths)
It's good with cucumber.
(Their appetite explodes.)
(You Seok picks up a perilla leaf.)
Jung Ah.
(Adding a slice of meat...)
(and a piece of You Seok's pickled onion)
- For Jung Ah who worked hard.
- Open up.
Have a wrap.
(Open up)
(What about me?)
How about a lettuce wrap?
In the US, we like perilla leaves more than lettuce.
In the US, people don't eat perilla leaves.
- Wait. Hold on.
- In the US...
Here's the thing about perilla leaves.
- I know this one thing.
- I had no idea.
Many foreigners think perilla leaves taste weird...
- just like cilantro.
- That's true.
- Not many eat perilla leaves.
- Because of its strong scent.
Anyway, I'll make it with a perilla leaf.
- In California, where I lived...
- I think...
I think she's a fraud.
She told me she got 1-on-1 lessons...
from Matt Damon.
- From Matt Damon?
- Yes.
(Speechless)
It was a wild boar, not Matt Damon.
- A wild boar?
- She got lessons from a wild boar.
(While they're laughing, a wrap for Jennica is ready.)
Thank you very much.
(Just watching Jennica makes me laugh.)
This one is for our youngest member.
- I'll make a wrap for Yoon Seo.
- Really?
Yes.
(Stuffing the vegetable wrap with so much delicious food)
- Here you go.
- Perfect.
There you go.
I'll make one for You Seok this time.
I'll make it.
I'll put what I want in my own vegetable wrap.
Really? Will you make one for me?
I was going to do it by myself.
(She makes a vegetable wrap for him in return.)
Thank you.
(Stuffing his mouth with the huge wrap)
(The youngest members always bicker,)
(but they look out for each other.)
(Everything on the table is delicious.)
(They can't stop eating.)
(They enjoy tonight's dinner.)
Seriously...
I've been eating so well since we came here.
When the viewers watch us eat...
- They must be...
- If they haven't eaten anything,
- they must crave this food.
- They can just get it delivered.
- The delivery is so fast.
- Right. They can get it delivered.
I think it's attached to this.
(Scratching)
Shall I remove the hair pieces now?
It feels like...
there's a bear on my head.
It's time to say goodbye to the aunt from the US.
Aunt Jennica is leaving for the US.
Is she leaving now?
- Yes, she's leaving.
- Aunt Jennica is leaving?
I've never heard the name Jennica.
- It's usually Jennifer or...
- It's...
Jessica and another name got mixed up.
- Jessica and...
- Jennifer.
- I feel much better now.
- She's going back to being herself.
- Sun Young, where have you been?
- Sun Young is back.
Bye, Aunt Jennica.
It feels good. It feels so refreshing.
My lips are driving me crazy.
(Meanwhile, Jung Ah's lips are driving her crazy.)
The staying power of your lipstick is incredible.
Your liner and lipstick are still intact.
- They look just perfect.
- Indeed.
Whenever I looked at you, I was amazed as you looked so pretty.
Right. I know.
The red lipstick.
(Red)
(Jeans)
Isn't there a song about a red lipstick that goes like this?
A red lipstick?
(The youngest sings Lee Hi's "Red Lipstick," released in 2021.)
- Is it an old song?
- "Pink Lipstick..."
- There's "Pink Lipstick."
- Oh, "Pink Lipstick?"
(The melody just slips out.)
(I will forget tomorrow)
- I will forget everything - I will forget everything
(The song naturally transitions into another song.)
("With Dark Lipstick" by Lim Ju Ri, 1987)
- You don't know this song, right?
- No.
- They really don't know...
- Does anyone know that song?
(Immersed in the song)
(The older members sing together.)
What's the title of this song?
(How come you don't know this song?)
She's using the hair pieces as a mic.
(Jennica turned into a mic.)
You guys really don't know the song.
Is it really okay for us to work together?
They sure are from a different generation.
(They finished dinner while feeling the generation gap.)
(Sun Young came inside to tidy up.)
Because we left the door open,
there are like 1,000 moths in here.
My gosh. A lot of them came inside.
- Gosh. What is this...
- Did we leave the door open?
- What's this mess?
- I wish we'd closed our room doors.
This is a total mess. What should we do?
Look up there. Those are all mosquitoes.
What do we do?
There are so many of them.
- My gosh. Look at all those moths.
- Gosh, seriously.
This is crazy.
- We have to catch all of them.
- The window...
Jung Ah.
This is war against bugs.
(Fresh Pest Control responds to the scene.)
(The girls' room)
(The living room)
(Their only goal is the total extermination of bugs.)
- It's funny that we're doing this.
- This is too much.
(Jung Ah stays focused with the red lipstick still on.)
(Swatting)
There's a mosquito here.
(Rushing)
- Where is it?
- I caught it.
I killed it.
These bugs are coming out endlessly.
(After spending a lot more time catching the bugs...)
There will probably be even more bugs next month.
(They clean up the mess as well. They're finally free from bugs.)
Let's see how it turns out.
We're caught all of them. I'm sure of it.
(The war against bugs is over.)
- Cheers, You Seok.
- Good job today.
(They're finally having a relaxing time.)
(Drowsy)
Hey, are you sleepy?
No, it's my eyes. My eyes are...
- It's because of your eye makeup.
- I can just pop in some eye drops.
- You didn't...
- I have eye drops for itchy eyes.
- Just a second.
- I have eye drops.
(You Seok rummages through his bag looking for something.)
Hey, put this on before going to bed.
- Oh, my. Thank you.
- You didn't...
- You didn't do it last night.
- No, I didn't. Thank you.
- Make sure to put it on.
- I'll take this.
- I'm grateful for this.
- Put that warm eye mask on.
I'm grateful for this.
- You should take a shower.
- Exactly.
You can take a shower first.
I think she's done showering.
Gosh. My back hurts.
On our 1st trip, those 3 days...
felt quite long in a good way. I could relax and enjoy the shoot.
But the past three days here...
- Time passed so quickly.
- Yes, indeed.
- That must be why I feel this way.
- But as the shoot goes on,
it'll feel like time is going by even more quickly.
You're sad that the night is slipping away...
(After tonight)
(We'll have to part ways again)
- The lyrics are just our story.
- Exactly.
(The words of the song resonate deeply with them.)
(Everyone is drenched in sadness.)
This is my final look at the yard.
It's sad. I really like this house.
- This house is nice, isn't it?
- Yes, this one.
- It's good.
- Stop looking at it now.
You Seok, aren't you going to take a shower?
- Come on. Leave him be.
- He just wants to...
- Look at his hair.
- Earlier in the afternoon...
- His hair is stiff from hairspray.
- Let me tell you something.
- Go ahead.
- I can take a shower now.
(Then go and take a shower.)
- Go on. We'll wait for you.
- When I'm back, you'll be gone.
(Crying out in sadness)
- Oh, you're sad to say goodbye.
- When I'm back from the shower,
you'll stay here for like five minutes...
and then say we should all go to bed.
- I'll wait until you go to bed.
- No.
I hate that you're the only one here.
What do you mean? Of course, I should take a shower by myself.
No, I mean I hate that...
you're the only dirty one here. Go and take a shower.
I'm going to take a shower later.
- I'm not saying I won't.
- When you're back from the shower,
we can all have some beer together...
- before going to bed.
- That's right.
We don't have any beer left.
- We still have beer.
- We have a lot of beer.
- What's wrong with you?
You guys are so loud.
See?
He likes to chat with us,
so he's afraid we might go to bed early.
- He's afraid of being left alone.
- He doesn't want us to be gone...
- when he's back from the shower.
- He thinks we might be gone.
- That's right.
- I see.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll wait until you come back and then drink beer.
- Are you going to drink more?
- Don't you worry.
- I'll be back shortly.
- We won't leave you alone.
(Finally, Anxiety goes to take a shower without worrying.)
You Seok must be really sad to wrap this up.
- You see, earlier...
- As if he had separation anxiety.
He teared up earlier...
while we were talking about how fast time passed by here.
(He must be sad.)
Does You Seok have no friends?
Come on.
Jung Ah, you're the logical type.
You didn't even blink when I was crying.
After our final shoot for "Love, Take Two,"
you left without even looking back.
It wasn't like that.
- I just told you how he reacted.
- Then what was it?
It doesn't change how I talk or act, does it?
I was just stating the fact.
Should we take him home with us?
What should we do with him?
He can stay at your place and mine for a month each.
I don't think I can live with him for a month.
- Really?
- My daughter will be uncomfortable.
After we finish the final shoot, You Seok will...
(You Seok comes back after the shower.)
(Spotting something)
You said you wouldn't drink it before I came back.
- It wasn't my decision.
- It's not a big deal.
Gosh, seriously.
- I promised...
- I knew it.
I made a promise to you.
- But Choon Ja...
- It wasn't like that.
We have to wake up at 8:30am.
- We have to wake up then?
- Yes.
- You can get up at 9am.
- Okay.
- Then I'll get up at 9am.
- All right.
I have to wait until my kids come home before going to bed.
Right.
No, that's not the case.
(They didn't waste a single moment of their second night in Taean.)
(And the next day)
(Everyone is still sleeping soundly.)
(Scratching)
(He falls back asleep.)
(It's another peaceful morning.)
(Current time: 8:27am)
(There's about 1 hour left until wake-up time.)
(At the same time, in the yard...)
(The staff members are moving around suspiciously.)
(They carefully enter the yard.)
(They're preparing something secretly.)
(The cast members are sleeping soundly.)
(Cock-a-doodle-doo)
What's going on?
(Am I dreaming?)
My gosh. That...
That startled me to death.
(Now that she's awake, she does techno dance.)
What time is it now?
But at 9:30am...
- At 9:30am... Sorry?
- We were going to make breakfast.
We planned to make breakfast at 9:30am.
(Trying to figure out the situation in their natural state)
(The staff makes an announcement.)
Sorry?
I can't hear you.
- What did you say?
- What did she say?
I haven't even drawn on my eyebrows.
(The quiet yard suddenly turned into a club.)
What did you say?
(Perking up his ears in front of the door)
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo, please wake up immediately.)
You said we could sleep until 9:30am.
(Upset)
Jung Ah and Yoon Seo,
please wake up immediately.
What's their problem? This is driving me crazy.
This is ridiculous.
(Laughing)
- You woke me up...
- You're ridiculous.
Why would you tell us a lie?
What's wrong with you?
Oh, I get it.
- It's only 8:30am...
- I just figured it out.
What is it?
Guys.
It's what we did yesterday.
- Had we known, we wouldn't have...
- I can't find my shoes.
(Grumbling)
drunk beer last night.
(Messy hair)
Right, Jung Ah?
Of course.
I have no makeup on.
What's going on? Why would you lie to us?
(You said the wake-up time was 9:30am.)
They're liars.
- What do you want us to do?
- Shall we give them another chance?
Yesterday,
you dressed up in retro style and posed for photos.
- Yes.
- The staff members had a poll...
with those photos of yours yesterday.
- What poll? Gosh, seriously.
- I told you so.
You had a poll?
(Just a day ago, they took a peaceful family photoshoot.)
(They thought it was to make good memories.)
(But with their individual photos,)
(the secret poll began among the staff members.)
(My goodness! Who's the best dresser that impressed you?)
(Contestant 1: Jung Ah)
(The 1970s' modern girl with romantic and unconventional vibes!)
(Passionate red stockings)
(Yum Jung Ah, the original Miss Korea diva)
(Contestant 2: Jennica)
Yes, this is the true scent of Korea.
(The icon of the 1970s hippie vibe, soaked in American culture)
(Jennica, the aunt who returned from the US)
(Contestant 3: You James Dean)
(The double denim look and a red scarf)
(You James Dean, the Western tough guy)
(Contestant 4: Roh Yoon Sunny)
(The bold mix of denim overalls and a red bandana is the key feature.)
(Roh Yoon Sunny from the girl group S.O.S)
(The 1st Siblings' Fashion Leader Contest)
Vote for the best fashion leader. Each one has one vote.
(The contestants' fate depends on the voting results.)
- She's sweeping the votes.
- This is the true retro style.
- I'm voting for the red colour.
- The red colour?
The double denim look is the ultimate fashion style.
The face is what completes a fashion style.
- I'm voting for Jung Ah.
- I choose Sun Young.
I'm voting for You Seok.
- Yoon Seo looks great.
- I'm voting for Yoon Seo.
(It continued until sunset. Here are the results.)
(My goodness! Who's the best dresser that impressed you?)
(Jung Ah: 22, Sun Young: 34, You Seok: 25, Yoon Seo: 17)
(3rd place, 1st place, 2nd place, 4th place)
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo are in the bottom two.)
The bottom two are going for additional work today.
Additional work?
(We're saved.)
(Jumping up and down with joy)
- Sun Young, we made it.
- You Seok, great job.
- Is that why you called us out?
- Yes.
(Closing her eyes)
(She's in denial.)
(Aunt Jennica's style was unbeatable.)
(Satisfied)
The 2 of you have 5 minutes to get ready.
- Come on. Five minutes?
- Five minutes is too short.
(The cut throat world of competition)
We'll give you ten minutes. Hurry up.
- You Seok.
- We harvested onions.
- My advice was helpful, wasn't it?
- I'm glad I took your advice.
- You should be.
- We're saved.
That's right. You did well.
By the way, where did that noise come from?
The noise from earlier. It terrified me.
I thought I was having a nightmare.
Play it one more time.
(She chuckles as she says, "Play it one more time.")
(Here goes "Cock-A-Doodle-Doo Song" once again.)
What now?
(What now? What is it?)
(They already got used to "Cock-A-Doodle-Doo Song.")
This song is so exciting.
I thought it was going too peacefully.
I get it. It's clear now. On the last day,
two of us are bound to get dragged somewhere for extra work.
- It was the same last time. Right?
- Yes.
What a relief. We're saved.
There must be tension in the air in that room right now.
I'll stay here until Jung Ah leaves.
(She's now walking on eggshells.)
(At the same time, the girls' room)
But why are we in the bottom two?
I have nothing to say about that.
(Laughing)
I hate you, Sun Young.
Gosh. I'm so upset.
Sun Young, don't laugh at us.
(Laughing)
Sun Young.
Be safe. I'll see you later.
- Shall I give you a massage?
- It will be tough.
Forget it!
I'm not upset about going there.
- Then what?
- How come You Seok beat me...
- Gosh.
- Is that what you're upset about?
That's what I'm upset about.
But I really did my best yesterday.
Maybe my vibe... I think I beat you with my energy.
- You Seok. Hey.
- Yes?
- Be quiet and fold the blankets.
- Okay.
- Read the room, will you?
Get up right now.
Jung Ah must be really tired now.
- Gosh, I'm upset.
- You don't seem upset.
You don't look upset at all.
Sun Young is so happy right now...
that she's smiling from ear to ear.
You guys won't be just chilling either.
- We should make breakfast.
- We'll make delicious dishes.
- Anything will be fine.
- We should make something nice.
(They're ready to go to work.)
By the way, how many votes did I get?
I was supposed to at least place second.
It's because I didn't look funny. I looked just pretty. Right?
Because I didn't look funny, right?
(Absolutely)
(She failed because she looked too pretty.)
- Let's get going, Yoon Seo.
- Okay.
(Receiving a beverage from You Seok)
- See you later.
- Should we go now?
- Jung Ah, see you later.
- Bye, Yoon Seo.
- Come back in one piece.
Sun Young, you swept the votes.
(He checks the rankings to the last moment.)
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo head to the unknown workplace.)
It must be potato or...
He mentioned a chicken farm because of the chicken song.
Blue crab? No, I don't think that's it.
(Or blue crab?)
(Where is today's workplace that awaits the two of them?)
Yes, we're going. It's just...
I had a feeling that we wouldn't be just chilling before going home.
I wonder where we're heading.
(Where are they being dragged to?)
(What place will they be working at?)
(Current time: 8:50am)
(The winners are enjoying a relaxing time.)
(Yawning)
(How much longer will you keep yawning?)
(She's letting out a long yawn, looking so relaxed.)
Oh, my. This is so nice.
I had no idea not working could feel...
this good.
(Yawning)
(She gives another long yawn.)
(And then, she makes iced coffee in a relaxed manner.)
Viewers,
I've been chosen.
I placed first.
(Happy)
(Giggling)
(He stops and watches her in sheer joy.)
- How about a cup of...
- What are you doing?
- Sun Young, you...
- I was bragging to the viewers.
But...
Unbelievable. Sun Young, come over here.
Come to think of it,
you placed 1st, and I placed 2nd at the curry showdown too.
- That's right.
- You always place first.
(The deity of victory is on our side.)
I just realised it.
We have good energy. We should stick together.
Exactly. We should...
- But if we keep winning...
- You dropped this.
We should look after Yoon Seo since she's the youngest.
- Let's help her from now on.
- Okay.
- Let's help her win next time.
We should take better care of the youngest member.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Starting from the next shoot, - Should I work instead of her?
- do worse than her no matter what.
- No.
- I'll do my best to win.
- Yoon Seo and I...
- What about Yoon Seo?
- She...
- Do you want her to work again?
- She and I can be in the top two.
- Okay.
And you should work.
I'm not sure I can do that.
(I'll be in the first place no matter what.)
(Let's just enjoy this relaxing time for now.)
That's funny.
(Yoon Seo washed up and is feeling refreshed.)
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
Are we going to start cooking at 9am?
- Why? Are you the planning type?
- No.
Can I do some exercise?
(He'll exercise instead of cooking?)
At 9am?
I'm going out for a jog until 9am.
Okay, I don't mind.
But after I'm back by 9am,
showering will take ten minutes. Is that okay?
I'm fine with it.
We've got plenty of time.
- That's right.
- Okay, I'm off.
I'm off for a jog.
Jung Ah and...
Yoon Seo have gone to work.
It can't be helped. Those who won have a life too.
Hi, this is You Seok.
Today...
(He's even shooting a solo video.)
While jogging, I'll show you...
nature, the sky,
and me.
(Leaving meal prep for later, he heads to the beach.)
Nature is a must...
for people.
(You Seok arrived at a nearby beach.)
(A video is a must.)
What a superb view.
(A wide-open sea that refreshes the soul)
Look at how clear the water is.
(Even the crystal-clear, shimmering seawater)
(While he relaxes and enjoys the moment,)
(forgetting all about making breakfast)
I'm going to draw my eyebrows.
This is me trying to draw my eyebrows.
Because I look too pale,
I'm doing this to remove extra makeup.
(Kim Sun Young's "Get It Beauty")
Think of it as giving them some depth.
My makeup artist said...
to start with my right.
(With idling away so much,)
(can they make breakfast before Jung Ah and Yoon Seo come?)
A doggy.
Where are we? What are we doing?
(Clucking)
The sound of chickens is...
I can actually hear chickens.
- It's chickens.
- Really?
(A place with chickens clucking?)
(This very place where chickens happily roam free)
(Sure-footed strides)
(A proud comb)
(A plump rear)
(Today's workplace: A chicken farm)
Chicken? What could we do with them? Collect eggs?
Chickens...
- It'll be my first...
- Aren't we scared of chickens?
It'll be my first time seeing real chickens.
(Worried even before encountering the chickens)
(Carefully entering the chickens' home)
Could that chicken be the boss?
What do we do with these guys?
Here, you'll be collecting...
fertilized eggs with shell number one.
Nice.
Can we take some home?
- Really?
- Number one.
I always buy number one eggs.
(A chicken farm in the heart of nature)
As you can see, I let the chickens roam around freely.
I never close the chicken coop doors.
(Free-range chickens raised with the coop doors left open)
They get to eat what they want...
and lay eggs when they want to. That's how they're kept.
(That's what makes these...)
(number 1 shell-marked eggs possible.)
Hi.
- Hi.
- Are you here for the eggs?
- Yes.
My gosh. I can't give them to you for free.
No, of course not.
- First, the chickens...
- They must be fed first.
Correct.
(On the way to cut grass for the chickens)
We're heading to where the grass is.
That's where pumpkins were planted.
The pumpkins will be harvested in autumn...
for the chickens to eat in winter.
Is this field for the chickens' food?
Yes, solely to feed the chickens.
They sure eat the good stuff.
- Right? They eat...
- The chickens eat quality food.
So the eggs are from chickens that eat quality food.
(Arrived at the grass-cutting spot)
Leave the cart here.
- Let me demonstrate.
- Okay.
You may hurt your hand if you grab the grass...
too close to the bottom.
Grab the grass around here and cut it.
(A few swipes of the sickle, and it's done.)
Do we not pull the roots out?
You can just cut the top parts.
- Does it grow back?
- Yes, it does.
Please fill a whole cart with grass.
- Okay.
- Like so. Try it.
(The two cut grass as instructed.)
Be careful of the sickle when you pull it towards you.
Got it.
(Cutting grass? It's not hard.)
(Cutting one blade of grass after another and stacking it up)
Like this.
(The two fill up the cart diligently.)
Grass like this one?
(Meanwhile, Yoon Seo is...)
What kind of grass is this? It looks interesting.
It sure looks interesting.
(Exclaiming)
(Yoon Seo also works hard.)
(The more they cut,)
(the more grass is stacking up for the chickens' snack.)
Like this.
(Tug-of-war with the grass)
(Yoon Seo got the trophy after much tug-of-war.)
(Groaning)
(A handful after much trouble)
Thinking how the chickens will enjoy this...
(Becoming energetic at the thought of feeding the chickens)
- It's nice.
- Expensive grass?
- So they can eat it more easily?
- Yes.
(Another handful...)
(so that the chickens can enjoy it to their hearts' content)
(After all that cutting,)
(the cart is piled high with grass.)
(Now it's time to feed the chickens.)
(Following)
Oh, my. I guess the chickens know...
- it's snack time.
- Come this way.
They know it's snack time.
(Having heard the news, the customers gather.)
(Snacks!)
(Hearing the news, the chickens line up even before the grass arrives.)
- Get out of the way. Move.
- Come on.
It's dangerous.
(Running)
(A flock of chickens comes flocking in like a cloud.)
- Okay. Place it there.
- Wait.
Place some around.
(Got a big piece)
- Look at these guys.
- How cute!
(The chickens are munching away.)
(Seeing them dig in makes them happy)
(The snack lady is hard at work.)
This is really amusing.
Dig in.
How cute.
Enjoy, okay?
Come this way.
(Thanks for the food!)
Give me a second. Let's see.
I'm sorry.
(Not a single foot of space to spare)
The crowd is making things hard.
Give me a little space.
The grass is over here, guys.
Come here, not there.
(Grass Yoon Seo scattered)
There's a bunch here.
(The customers are gathered in a different spot.)
Come over here.
- Here's some grass.
- Food.
Follow me.
Will they eat if I serve it to them?
Come over here.
Here. Dig in.
(It's yummy grass!)
(Eating the fresh grass)
They look cute.
- What?
- They look cute,
- They sure dig in.
- looking closely.
I thought I'd be scared of them.
(Being charmed by the chickens while feeding them)
They're enjoying it.
- Dig in! Enjoy!
- Dig in!
Enjoy!
(Done feeding the chickens grass)
- We'll be collecting eggs.
- Okay.
I'm leaving.
When collecting eggs,
try not to talk.
- Speak softly.
- Okay.
Place the big eggs around the cart...
- and small eggs in the center.
- The center?
The pointy end should face down.
Down.
(Place the eggs pointy end down.)
(There's an air pocket at the rounded end, so storing eggs...)
(with the pointed end down helps keep them fresh.)
(Eggs will be collected from three complexes today.)
(Complexes 1, 2, 3)
- Follow me.
- Okay.
Try not to talk, if possible.
The chickens are waiting to lay eggs...
- right now.
- I see.
- This way.
- They're giving birth right now.
I'll talk very softly.
This way.
(Entering the henhouse to collect fresh eggs)
Let me show you.
(Slowly reaching in so the chickens don't get startled)
If you push in very slowly, it's okay.
(Gently take the eggs out, and that's it.)
(Most importantly, make sure not to startle the chickens.)
It just laid this one. It's a freshly laid egg.
(Secured freshly laid eggs)
- Like this.
- A freshly laid egg.
Excuse me.
You have to place your hand inside and grab the egg out.
(Flying off)
(Screaming)
I'm sorry.
(I had to be quiet, but I couldn't.)
Try placing your hand inside.
(Trying again)
Check if there are any eggs.
- Are there?
- It's warm.
That's it. That's how you do it.
(She successfully collected her first eggs!)
Just like that.
(This time, Yoon Seo tries alone.)
(Touching)
There are three in here. I'm sorry. Excuse me for a bit.
(Collected 3 eggs in 1 go)
The pointy end down.
(Meanwhile, how's Jung Ah doing?)
(Hesitating)
(Jung Ah has always been scared of animals.)
(Staring)
(Confronting it without reaching in)
(She spotted an empty nest.)
(After reading the chicken's face,)
(she quickly gets one egg while the chicken is gone.)
(Jung Ah contributed by adding an egg.)
She can't do it.
- I can't lift it up.
- No.
I can't put my hand inside.
- You can't?
- No.
Right here.
(Spotted an empty nest)
Only the visible ones.
- Only the visible ones.
- Yes.
(Jung Ah targets the nests that are empty.)
There's a bunch here. After laying them...
(Did the chicken go somewhere?)
How kind of it.
(Collecting the eggs while the chicken is gone)
(Filled up a carton by collecting eggs from empty nests)
I'm sorry.
Okay.
(Feeling bad about collecting the eggs)
I'm sorry.
(Yoon Seo is being gentle so as not to scare the chicken.)
(My eggs...)
It's giving birth right now.
I should be careful.
Put the pointed end down.
(Clucking)
(Startled)
That scared me. Gosh.
(1 egg)
It might peck at me.
(Scared but continuously working)
There are three here.
(3 eggs)
Hold on.
You're doing well.
It's your calling.
- Really?
- Yes.
All right.
Did you collect a lot, Jung Ah?
I only need one more egg to fill a carton.
(Moving to the next complex while pulling the egg cart)
Pardon me.
That's it.
Well done.
Excuse me.
(She even collects the eggs the chickens are brooding.)
(3 eggs)
(Being careful)
I'm sorry.
Gosh, four eggs? You laid a lot.
There are five!
(Found an egg bonanza)
(Already quite skilled with her hands)
This one's slightly small.
(Jung Ah is trying again.)
(Startled)
(Collecting the egg quickly while the chicken is away)
(Checking out the next empty nest)
(It looked like an empty nest, but the owner appeared.)
(But she's still targeting empty nests.)
Quickly.
(Knowing how Jung Ah feels, the chicken makes way.)
(Frozen)
Oh, my gosh.
It's far inside.
(The owner is inside the nest.)
(She reaches for the egg while holding her breath.)
(Anxious)
(Collected only an egg)
(Breathing out)
(Current time: 10am)
(Team Home hasn't even started cooking.)
Gosh.
What are you doing, Sun Young?
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Welcome back.
- Thanks.
(Can they really be taking their time?)
I don't know what I'll make,
but let's get to it now.
Let's go.
I must make breakfast without Jung Ah today.
(Raised in Taean's pristine tidal flats)
(The second dish made with the plump, chewy clams)
- For the soft tofu stew, - Yes?
it only takes 20 minutes to cook.
(And with the eggs collected by Jung Ah and Yoon Seo)
Next, rolled omelet.
What were we going to make? Soft tofu stew. Rolled omelet.
(You Seok and Sun Young's to-do list)
(Cook rice, prep ingredients for rolled omelet,)
(cook Manila clam soft tofu stew)
I'd better cut up the vegetables...
for the rolled omelet right now, right?
Okay, I'll finely chop the vegetables for the rolled omelet.
(The first ingredient prep without Jung Ah)
Vegetables.
Onions.
Do we add chilli to the rolled omelet?
(Do we add chilli...)
(to the rolled omelet?)
Chilli is too spicy.
Let's not put it in.
(Who is she talking to?)
Green onions and...
(Green onions?)
Should I chop up these green onions for the rolled omelet...
or spring onions that are thinner?
Okay, let's use spring onions.
(She once again solves the question by answering it herself.)
Spring onions.
Carrots. Carrots are a must.
Okay.
(Let's get to washing the ingredients.)
(Washing the dirty roots of the spring onions first)
Do I throw this part out or what?
What am I supposed to do?
This part is inedible. Throw it out.
Or is it an important part?
(It's actually the most nutritious part.)
(Sun Young just cuts it off.)
(She moves on to the onion next.)
We'd better cook rice.
(While peeling the onion,)
(she even cuts the normal parts.)
(A cooking novice awkwardly prepping vegetables)
(While Sun Young is prepping the ingredients and making huge losses)
Okay.
(Before cooking the soft tofu stew,)
(You Seok starts with the rice.)
Rice...
One cup is one portion.
We have four in total.
(He can easily cook rice.)
I should cook at least three portions.
(Since Jung Ah and Yoon Seo would've worked hard)
Let's add a little black rice and make black rice.
(You Seok brings it over to the sink.)
(Like a pro home cook,)
(he's skilled at washing the rice.)
(You Seok didn't waste a single grain of rice.)
(After eyeballing the amount of water)
(Slightly)
(Adding slightly more)
(Checking it for the last time on a flat surface)
(Satisfied)
(A pro home cook with serious solo-living skills)
Shall we get started? The vegetables.
Chopping these up is easy peasy.
(Chopping up the spring onions fast)
This size should be fine, right? About this size.
(These are not chives.)
This much should do.
Add in the spring onions.
Next, the onion.
(Moving on straight to the onion)
Onion.
I'd better chop it pretty. Jung Ah likes it pretty.
(Sun Young chops the onion finely and neatly.)
Like this, so that it turns out square.
(This doesn't look right.)
The onion...
will turn sweet when cooked,
so even if it's thick, it's easy to eat.
The onion looks too thick, though.
It's okay. The onion doesn't have to be cooked fully.
Next, the carrot.
Those back from work might not be pleased...
if they chew on carrots while eating the egg omelet.
I'll chop them finely.
(Sun Young basically minces the carrot.)
(But it's still big.)
Okay, all minced.
(Sun Young is quite pleased with it.)
Okay. The more carrots, the tastier.
All done.
(You Seok and Sun Young's to-do list)
(Cook Manila clam soft tofu stew)
(Meanwhile, did Jung Ah find another empty nest?)
(It's a nest with a chicken brooding on the egg!)
(Where did Jung Ah, who only went for empty nests, go?)
(Collecting eggs without any hesitation whatsoever now)
(Jung Ah has grown more confident in taking the eggs out.)
(1 egg)
The egg is warm because the chicken just laid it.
(Clucking)
(Jung Ah has become comfortable to the point of...)
(collecting eggs that the chickens are brooding.)
(Thoughtfully moving away)
(3 eggs)
(Thanks to it, Jung Ah collects the egg easily.)
Just one.
(Even moving away for Yoon Seo)
(There are a whopping 5 eggs!)
It's a party of eggs!
- All done.
- Yes.
They must know we're here for the eggs.
- The chickens?
- Yes, they stay still.
Let's gather them.
(However, the eggs are different in size.)
Are they classified as extra-large...
- or large based on their size?
- Yes.
But we don't classify them as much.
- See how the colours are different?
- Yes.
The colours are what matter.
Depending on what they are fed,
the yolk's colour changes.
So it changes depending on...
what the chickens eat.
- The colours are all different.
- Yes.
- It's a marker.
- This is what makes the egg...
free-range, number one.
Original eggs.
In short,
- the diverse colours are best.
- Exactly.
That's a useful tip.
Place yours on top. You collected more.
I'll pull it.
(Bye!)
Bye.
(Bye, chickens! Thanks for the eggs!)
They're cute.
Thank you.
(How many did the two collect?)
- One, two, three, - Yes.
four, five. Five cartons.
- Five cartons.
- Five cartons of eggs.
(The eggs collected by Jung Ah and Yoon Seo are...)
(placed on the machine with an adhesion device,)
(cleaned thoroughly, sorted out,)
(packed nicely in cartons, and delivered directly nationwide.)
Good work today.
- Thank you.
But...
- Really?
- Yes.
- Take these and enjoy them.
- They look really fresh.
Look how clean they are.
Thank you so much.
Let's have one each.
- This? Raw egg?
- Yes.
- Go ahead, if you'd like.
- You see,
I've never tried it before.
- Never?
- No.
- Me neither. Does it smell?
- First...
No. We're told our eggs don't smell,
but I personally don't eat raw eggs.
- But those who eat them...
- Why...
Why do you not eat them raw?
I can't because I'm squeamish.
Same here.
I'm not having one.
I've never tried it.
I like my eggs half-cooked.
- Half-cooked eggs are good.
- Right?
I heard it was flavourful.
- You heard from others?
- Yes.
This one is good. It was freshly laid.
But you've never tried one either.
Come on, it's for you.
- Do I...
- I blocked this side, okay?
Okay.
Drink it. Suck it out.
Oh, my.
(Yoon Seo is trying her very first raw egg.)
The taste is gone quickly, but it was savoury.
It was savoury.
- It's savoury.
- Yes.
I was surprised because it was a lot.
- I gave you a small one.
- It hits you hard.
Yes. That's why I was frowning.
(Laughing)
Thank you.
Good job.
Take it and enjoy it. You must be hungry.
- Thank you.
- Such precious eggs.
My throat is...
- Like lubricant... I should sing.
- You should sing.
- It'll make you sing.
- It's so smooth.
This much first. It's bothersome.
You better hurry.
Are they done?
Really? Is Jung Ah on the way?
(Suddenly hit with the bad news)
What?
(What they have ready so far...)
(is purple rice.)
(He leisurely went for a run...)
(and she leisurely put on makeup.)
You Seok, make soft tofu stew now.
The rolled omelet can be done real quick.
(He quickly takes the ingredients.)
Boil soft tofu.
(Running to the yard)
(The two grasshoppers are under the gun.)
- Are you going to cut them?
- Yes, I'll be quick.
They just left.
(He's in a hurry.)
Let's hurry up.
(Sun Young shuts her mouth and cuts the ingredients too.)
(Cutting super fast)
(They barely manage to prepare the ingredients.)
(All they need to do now is to stir-fry and boil them.)
(Picking up)
(There's no time for a break. He starts cooking immediately.)
(Here's how fast a home-cooked food master can go.)
(Apply oil on the pan first.)
You need to stir-fry green onions first.
You're making green onion oil? That's cool.
(Throwing in green onions)
(Flashy wrist snaps)
(Glancing)
You're good at cooking, You Seok.
(This is me.)
(You Seok looks like a master chef.)
(Adding chilli powder)
Green onion oil and chilli oil.
(Stir-fry it quickly with green onions.)
(Green onion and chilli oil for Manila clam soft tofu stew)
- I'm done.
- You're done?
- Okay.
I'm done.
(They can finish cooking before Jung Ah arrives.)
(He just needs to stir-fry onions before adding water.)
What?
- They're here. This is bad.
- Where?
(Team Poultry Farm has already arrived?)
Did they prepare the food?
Will it not be ready?
(Hungry Jung Ah is approaching.)
(But none of the dishes are ready.)
I shouldn't be doing this.
Do I cook rolled omelet there?
(Jung Ah arrives earlier than they thought.)
Is the rice ready?
(Panicked)
Hold on.
A big wok...
Wait, I don't need this.
This... Go back.
I want to eat soft tofu stew as soon as I arrive.
(Jung Ah arriving in 20 seconds)
(You Seok tries to finish it somehow.)
(He quickly stir-fries onions before she arrives.)
(He tries to add water at least.)
(Team Poultry Farm has arrived.)
(Gulping)
(What should I do?)
What...
- What are they doing?
- He's stir-frying something.
(Hold on...)
He's cooking.
Why does it look like...
he's stirring nothing with chopsticks?
(Jung Ah assesses the situation with a frown.)
(Sun Young comes out to the yard, pretending to be very busy.)
- Act busy.
Jung Ah, good job. Was it very tough?
Was it very tough?
- Yes.
- Oh, dear.
(Sun Young and You Seok greet them as if nothing was wrong.)
- You're back.
- Yes. Are you done?
I'm done. Go and change. I'm done.
(Really?)
(She checks right away with high expectations.)
(Peek)
Is it stir-fried onion?
Just you wait. I'm cooking soft tofu stew.
(Nothing is ready for breakfast.)
(At the scolding that will fall upon them,)
(the two grasshoppers are very nervous.)
The vegetables are ready. That...
It's all ready. I'll start making rolled omelet now.
(The wasp's attack makes her confused.)
- Should I cut green onions?
- What?
- Green onions?
- We're done.
There's nothing for you to do.
Go wash your hands and get changed. You worked hard.
(Team Poultry Farm is sent to the room by the wasp.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young and You Seok quickly prepare breakfast.)
I'm done. This is all.
(He just needs to add the seasoning and boil it.)
(He adds soy sauce to the stew base.)
(Stir-fry it until it nearly burns to increase umami.)
(Pouring water)
(It's starting to look like stew.)
(And the main ingredient of soft tofu stew)
(A generous amount of Manila clams)
(Boiling)
(Add zucchini too.)
(It looks perfectly like stew.)
(Sun Young quickly starts to make rolled omelets.)
Goodness.
I should've just gone to the poultry farm too.
The poultry farm looks fun.
(She cracks eggs while chatting.)
(When you crack the top notch eggs...)
(Bouncy)
The yolks are different.
They're fertilized eggs.
These are precious free-range eggs.
My goodness.
I get to eat such precious eggs.
I love it.
How many should I use?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
(More?)
(She must be making a huge rolled omelet.)
(Another egg?)
My gosh.
(How big is the rolled omelet going to be?)
(When she adds the cut vegetables...)
I just need to add salt and mix it.
I normally don't add a lot of vegetables.
Because it's hard to roll.
Done.
I'll start cooking free-range eggs rolled omelet.
(She's excited to eat free-range eggs rolled omelet.)
(She starts cooking by applying oil.)
(She pours a generous amount onto the pan.)
Anything tastes good with a lot of oil.
You need a lot of oil.
(Sloshing)
Is the fire too strong? Pour it in first.
Pour it in first.
(She pours the whole thing.)
(She pours 10 eggs onto an insane amount of oil.)
This is definitely going to fail.
Instead of rolled omelet, I should just...
- This is definitely going to fail.
- Sun Young...
Instead of rolled omelet, I should just...
- Wait, Sun Young.
- Why?
This white thing...
- It's being deep-fried.
- Is that oil? It's deep-frying...
(The edge of the rolled omelet stands up.)
(Because there's too much oil,)
(the edge became deep-fried right away.)
- Is that oil? It's deep-frying...
- Be quiet.
Don't say it. Be quiet. I'll finish it before Jung Ah comes.
(Despite what she said, she looks very concerned.)
Can this become rolled omelet?
(Out of worry, she speaks in dialect.)
It's deep-fried.
What should I do? This is bad.
(She doesn't know what to do with the turner.)
(Grinning)
It's deep-fried egg.
I hear you have deep-fried eggs in Taiwan.
(She rationalizes it as Taiwan-style deep-fried eggs.)
It looks delicious, though.
It looks delicious.
This looks delicious. It's being cooked.
(Brainwashing the viewers too)
It looks good.
(Will the rolled omelet be fine?)
(Footsteps)
(They feel a presence in the courtyard.)
(Is it Jung Ah?)
(Glancing)
(Thankfully, it's Yoon Seo, not Jung Ah.)
Hey.
- No.
- What is it?
Nothing.
(Jung Ah is getting ready while humming.)
(Her heart sank for a moment because she thought it was Jung Ah.)
- What is it, Sun Young?
- It's nothing.
I must finish this before Jung Ah comes out.
(She sees the rolled omelet.)
(Rolled... omelet?)
Is this steamed egg?
It's rolled omelet.
It's not steamed egg.
(Trying to laugh)
It's rolled omelet. It's not steamed egg.
(Rolled omelet?)
No...
Go and stop her from coming out.
Yoon Seo, go and ask Jung Ah to do something for you.
Because you want to finish it before she comes out?
Yes. She'll get upset...
- when she sees this.
- Or...
- She's coming out soon.
- Go ask her to do something.
(She's coming out soon?)
(Rushing)
(I can't let her see that.)
(She quickly gets a turner!)
Hey.
(Move, everyone.)
(She quickly starts to roll it.)
- The eggs...
- This is bad.
(There's too much beat eggs, so they overflow to the side.)
This is bad.
I'll get a lot of scoldings for ruining such precious eggs.
(Mushy)
Sun Young.
We just got the eggs...
I know, I'm sorry.
We brought them with so much effort.
(Having a slight mental breakdown)
Can steamed egg be half-cooked?
Rolled omelet, I mean. You can have it half-cooked, right?
You can have it half-cooked, right?
- I can do it. My back.
- The eggs are gone.
(Exhaustion, 10.87 percent, Sadness: 4 percent,)
(Fear: 82.8 percent, Joy: 2.33 percent)
(Can she salvage the rolled omelet?)
I can make this similar to rolled omelet.
I just need to cut it. Right?
(She cooks the thick rolled omelet thoroughly.)
It looks good. It smells different.
It looks so good. All you need is this and rice.
One.
(She takes out half of the well-cooked rolled omelet.)
It looks tasty.
(Laughing)
Here.
I'll cut these like rolled omelets.
These will be like pancakes.
A traditional holiday vibe.
(Brainwashing them)
(When the rolled omelets have cooled down a bit...)
These are jumbo rolled omelets. They're popular in Taiwan.
(She cuts it quickly before Jung Ah comes out.)
(Place them on the plate neatly.)
(It does look pretty legit.)
It's perfect.
(Sun Young is excited at her perfect crime.)
(At that moment, Jung Ah appears.)
(Shocked)
(She suddenly gets nervous.)
I just need to add soft tofu now.
(She checks Manila clam soft tofu stew first.)
(It's only 80 percent done.)
- Shall I add more water?
- Yes, there's too little water.
(She adjusts the water level without commenting much.)
Here's the water.
What's that? Egg...
(She spots the rolled omelet.)
Rolled omelet. I made pancakes with some too.
I'm going to fry some now too.
(She stutters in nervousness.)
(She's walking on eggshells too.)
(I see...)
What is it?
(Does she not like it?)
What is it? I rolled it myself.
It looks nice, right?
(She got two thumbs ups.)
(Grinning widely)
(The rolled omelet is complete.)
(Let's quickly finish Manila clam soft tofu stew.)
(To finish cooking breakfast quickly,)
(Jung Ah helps them out.)
(She cuts soft tofu into big pieces.)
(Next to her, You Seok...)
(adds oyster mushrooms...)
(and boil them nicely.)
(You Seok lets Jung Ah check the stew.)
It's going to be bland.
(Slurping)
(How does You Seok's stew taste?)
- It's bland.
- Right?
(When the stew is bland...)
(Chef Yum's tip: Add salted shrimp to add umami as well.)
(She adds another spoonful to season it perfectly.)
(Lastly, add soft tofu.)
(It became a lot tastier with Captain Yum's help.)
(Manila clam soft tofu stew is done.)
Shall we add salted shrimp?
(Breakfast is ready, but Yoon Seo sits in front of the fire?)
(With the free-range eggs they got from the morning labour...)
The oil is shifting to one side.
(Yoon Seo is making fried eggs.)
(Checking the temperature)
It looks good.
(She drops one after another onto the heated pan.)
(Since they're precious eggs, she cooks 1 per person.)
(No salt, no pepper)
(Only pure love)
(When the backside is cooked,)
(she flips it casually and coolly.)
(Even though it looks rough, she doesn't pop the yolks.)
(Move them onto the plate, and it's complete.)
- You Seok, scoop it up now.
- Okay.
You don't need help?
(They're finally setting the table for breakfast.)
(Soft tofu stew...)
(tastes better when it's from an earthenware bowl.)
(He fills up the bowl.)
(He adds one free-range egg without saving it.)
(Head chef You Seok's masterpiece, Manila clam soft tofu stew)
(It looks even more legit with the ketchup.)
(Sun Young's masterpiece, free-range eggs jumbo rolled omelet)
(She prepared a holiday-vibe egg pancakes too.)
(Fried eggs with bright yellow egg yolks)
(A fabulous breakfast is ready.)
- Let's try the egg first.
- I want to try fried eggs too.
- Fried eggs.
- Yes, fried eggs.
I'm curious.
(How does the fried egg taste?)
(Amazed)
Is it tasty?
It's so savoury.
Really?
(Jung Ah tries the fried egg too.)
(It melts away her frown.)
It sure is different.
- Really?
- It's sweet, even.
- Yes.
- The egg?
I didn't add any seasoning.
You added sugar, didn't you?
No, I added nothing.
It's sweet.
- I didn't...
- It's really sweet.
I didn't add any seasoning on purpose.
(Free-range eggs taste sweet because of its freshness.)
It's so good.
(Yoon Seo tries a bite too out of curiosity.)
Should I have cooked more?
(Let me try it too.)
(Satisfied)
Did you get the eggs freshly just now?
- Yes.
- It's so tasty.
Are they freshly laid?
Yes, this morning.
(Amazing!)
I can't believe I get to taste this.
(The fresh eggs are on a whole different level.)
The fried egg is so good.
(Now that they've comforted their stomachs with fried eggs,)
(let's try You Seok's Manila clam soft tofu stew.)
(Slightly nervous)
It's good.
(Yoon Seo tries You Seok's soft tofu too.)
- It's good, You Seok.
- It's so good.
It's delicious.
(At Sun Young and Yoon Seo's praises...)
Jung Ah cooked it all.
(I only helped with the seasoning.)
It's so good.
(Jung Ah takes a big spoonful with soft tofu.)
Good job.
It's delicious.
(Even Jung Ah is enjoying it.)
(Relieved)
The soup is nice and spicy.
It's so good.
(The Manila clam soft tofu stew is spicy and sharp.)
(She scoops up a spoonful of spicy Manila clam soft tofu stew.)
(Taking a bite with rice)
(Jung Ah has the soup with the egg.)
(She has it with soft tofu too.)
(And...)
Put fried egg on top.
(Yoon Seo is in love with Manila clam soft tofu stew.)
(One spoonful of rice with fried egg)
(One spoonful of soft tofu)
(One spoonful of soup)
(Eating nonstop)
(Clapping)
(It's the best.)
- You...
- It's her.
Jung Ah's touch.
(Double thumbs up)
- It's strange.
- Manila clam. I love it.
(This time, she shucks Manila clam.)
(Slurping with the soup)
(This place has mean soft tofu stew.)
(The youngest enjoys it.)
(Feeling proud)
Who cooked this?
- Sun Young did it, right?
- Yes.
- Yes, I cooked it.
- Let me try.
(As for this rolled omelet...)
(Drowned in a pond of oil because she used too much)
(The rolled omelet is somewhere in between steamed and deep-fried.)
(She even hid the cooking process in case Jung Ah scolded her.)
(Nervous)
I hope it's to your taste.
(How will Jung Ah find it?)
(Very nervous)
- How is it?
- It's good.
- Thanks.
- Jung Ah's touch.
You're good.
(Really?)
(Humming)
- I'm good at rolled omelets, right?
- Yes, you're good.
(She took it out as soon as it was cooked and degreased it.)
(Sun Young's rolled omelet became soft and moist.)
It's good.
(She finishes the piece she was eating.)
(She takes another piece.)
(Munching)
(It tastes good again.)
(Even Yoon Seo, who knows the cooking process,)
(takes a bite of the rolled omelet.)
(How did she do this?)
It's good.
(The consecutive compliments make her smile brightly.)
The rolled omelet tastes good.
(Sun Young relaxes and eats the rolled omelet too.)
(With the eggs they got from the morning labour...)
(and the dishes Sun Young and You Seok cooked,)
(the siblings recharge nicely.)
(They pull off their cooking debut without Jung Ah.)
Gosh.
(Sun Young falls deep in thought while eating.)
This morning was the most fun.
I love that kind of stuff.
You looked really happy.
(Still happy thinking about it)
(Annoyed)
Hey, we need to stay more alert.
- I know.
- It's fun for me.
(She can't believe it.)
Sun Young always takes first place when in any competition.
- I know.
- She dominates.
- That's me.
- She won the curry showdown too.
- Yes.
- I always rank near the bottom.
- You're near the bottom.
- But I took second place back then.
- No.
- She won, and I was the runner-up.
- It's okay, Yoon Seo.
- I'll let you win next time.
- You all are really talented.
Just wait. Okay?
- And you'll win it anyway.
- No, I...
I have a plan.
She has a plan.
- I'll make sure you win.
- It tickles so much, Sun Young.
(A sudden breath attack)
Her breath...
(Tickling)
drills into my ear.
(She's adorable.)
She's so cute.
Right? When I look at Yoon Seo, she's so adorable.
You're more adorable.
- What are you talking about?
- She's a positive person.
She's very positive.
- She's also very wise.
- Yes.
When was I ever wise?
You're very wise when you handle a situation.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Agreeing)
(Shy)
(When they're having breakfast peacefully...)
Do we boil the soy sauce?
- We boiled it, right?
- You boil soy sauce,
- vinegar, - I see.
- and sugar.
- Sugar.
- And add some water.
- Okay.
And boil it.
(A toy snake that looks familiar)
(The night before)
(A snake turned the siblings' house upside down.)
(A toy snake)
(It was their revenge for the sea squirt prank.)
(Please refer to Episode 1.)
(The production staff was humiliated big time.)
(Revenge breeds revenge.)
(Dreaming of the perfect revenge,)
(the camera boldly moves in on Jung Ah.)
(Approaching)
(It moves in a little closer.)
Okay.
It's basically 1 to 1 to 1, with just a bit more sugar.
(But no one cares.)
(Sighing)
(This isn't what we wanted.)
When it comes to a boil, the soy sauce becomes bitter.
Turn the heat off before it comes to a boil.
(It keeps hovering around Jung Ah.)
And then...
The soy sauce...
(Did he see it?)
(He didn't notice it.)
You're busy, though.
(Really? Do you still not see it?)
(Since it's not working,)
(it moves in more boldly.)
- When you're on set, - Be careful, Jung Ah.
focus on your performance.
(She finally finds it.)
I wanted to focus, but...
You need to act on set because you're an actor.
(But Jung Ah...)
(only smiles at the camera.)
You need to act on set because you're an actor.
I keep thinking about you two.
You can't keep thinking about our show.
Some emotions can't be controlled.
Is that so? Then, you can't help it.
- Look at the camera.
- Gosh.
- What's wrong with you all?
- Goodness.
(Jung Ah finally sees the snake.)
I can't believe these guys.
How many times are you going to reuse it?
Jung Ah, this isn't the first time.
Before... What was it? The Korean melons.
(She was going to grab some Korean melons this morning.)
Who put the snake here again?
(Peekaboo!)
Come on. When did they put it here?
Are there any special instructions?
Gosh. Darn it.
(Here we meet again.)
Gosh. For goodness' sake. Come here.
Who did it?
Gosh. I really need to throw it away.
(The production staff paid her back 3 times over.)
(Glaring)
Isn't it too petty?
It's such a petty attempt.
Gosh. Seriously.
I find it amazing now.
- We respect you.
- I really think you're amazing.
We respect you.
Just tell me one thing.
Who is the one coming up with these ideas?
- No. Let me tell you what happened.
- It's you, In Hyeok, right?
I think there's a separate team for it.
But they put...
(Laughing)
This is crazy.
It's ridiculous.
- I'm getting a dopamine rush.
- I can't believe them.
I needed that dopamine.
I'm getting a dopamine rush right now.
- What should we do?
- What an amazing team.
(Moved by the production staff)
Let's peel garlic. Hurry.
Okay.
- I'll do the dishes, You Seok.
- Okay.
Please help them with the garlic and Korean melons.
(Pulling)
(Rolling the pants so they won't get wet...)
(like a tough girl)
(Yoon Seo starts doing the dishes.)
(Scrubbing and focused)
(While Yoon Seo does the dishes...)
She is scrubbing hard.
I know. She is full of energy.
Gosh. Our Yoon Seo.
She's doing the dishes alone.
It's nothing.
- Is it nothing?
- Yes.
(No worries.)
(They leave the dishes to energetic Yoon Seo.)
(They hurry and prep the large amount of garlic.)
(As for the garlic they're peeling,)
(they harvested it the day before under the scorching sun.)
(Seosan's seasonal specialty is garlic.)
I can tell that the garlic is fresh.
- Yes.
- Yes, I can totally tell.
Taean's six-clove garlic.
(Seosan's garlic grown in sea breeze...)
(has large cloves and a rich aroma,)
(making it perfect for pickling.)
(However,)
(while the recipe is simple and tasty,)
(making pickled garlic requires lots of work...)
(because you have to peel each clove by hand.)
(That's why the two older sisters have become quiet.)
- When you peel garlic together...
- Yes.
I'm talking to the viewers.
Sorry. I responded.
(Sorry. I responded.)
When you peel garlic together, it brings you closer.
If you want to be closer to someone,
peel garlic together.
While spending time together,
you can talk about many things without rushing.
(You Seok preps the sauce for the pickled garlic.)
Now,
(Let's get into making the pickling sauce.)
I'm going to make the sauce with the soy sauce.
(You Seok, a home-cooking pro, who has lived alone for 10 years,)
(makes pickled vegetables at home frequently because he loves it.)
That's enough.
(He checks the amount of garlic before making the sauce.)
We'll have a little more than this.
Just a little.
- This is all, right?
- No.
- It's more than this.
- A little more?
Another third of the current amount will be added.
(Calculating the amount of the sauce)
(Finished calculating)
(Pickling is all about the ratio!)
(A home cook's tip)
(When you don't have a measuring cup,)
(get the ratio you want by using an ordinary cup!)
(He fills up the cup with soy sauce.)
(Then he pours it into the pot.)
(As for vinegar, water, and sugar,)
(pour an equal amount as soy sauce.)
(Pour them in a 1-to-1-to-1 ratio.)
Sugar needs to melt.
(You Seok's pickling sauce with the perfect ratio is ready!)
Can I pour it over now?
We're done.
(After peeling the garlic hard,)
Gosh.
(wash it with clean water.)
They peeled so many so quickly.
Exactly.
Do I peel it?
(After patting it dry completely,)
(he pours the boiled pickling sauce over it.)
(Pickled Seosan garlic made with You Seok's sauce)
(Pour the last of the sauce over the garlic.)
(The amount of You Seok's sauce is just perfect.)
Gosh. It's done.
(They'll pickle it for a month.)
Shall we get ready now? We're heading to the beach.
(As it's their last day in Taean,)
(the siblings decided to go enjoy the sea.)
- We need the instant camera.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- I got it.
Shall we?
- We'll get there by bicycle.
- Really?
- I'm kidding.
- Gosh.
- What's with you?
- Don't do this to me.
Come on. I was kidding.
(Don't leave me behind.)
Gosh. It's hot.
(Cheering up)
Okay. Shall we?
- Yes.
(They're off to see the sea!)
This is my first time seeing the sea this summer.
- Really?
- Yes.
Didn't we... That's right.
It's our first time going to the beach.
Didn't we...
Don't tell me we'll work when we get there.
Come on, Sun Young.
Are we not taking the photos for the posters?
- No way.
- That can't happen...
because I'm wearing slippers.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- What? Is that the sea or the sky?
- Gosh.
That's the sky. I thought it was the sea.
(While enjoying the amazing views around,)
(they drive through the dense forest.)
It's so pretty.
How did you find this spot?
- It's pretty.
- It's really pretty here.
- Gosh. The flowers are pretty too.
- Gosh.
Gosh. It's pretty.
Amazing.
(The beach entrance is covered with yellow flowers.)
Gosh. Look at the flowers.
(I can't believe there are flowers on the beach.)
(The blue sea of Taean unfolds beyond the golden tickseed.)
Goodness.
(The seemingly untouched, vast white beach...)
(and clear and transparent water)
(Taean's beautiful spot, Baengnipo Beach)
(With the unusual scenic view...)
It's pretty.
It's beautiful. Isn't it, Jung Ah?
It's so pretty.
Gosh.
(The siblings follow the golden tickseed to the beach.)
Is this the right way?
- Gosh.
- There are butterflies.
These flowers are so pretty.
(Butterflies gather around Yoon Seo, thinking she's a flower.)
Gosh. It's so pretty.
The sand is so warm.
It feels nice. I'm going to walk barefoot.
(She takes off her shoes as the sand is fine and soft.)
- Gosh. This place is so romantic.
- It's pretty.
The beach is best in summer.
Gosh. I love it.
It feels like the beach in European films...
where a family visits for a vacation.
Exactly.
The colour is so pretty.
- Gosh. The sky is beautiful too.
- I love it.
(They love it.)
Should we dip our feet in the water?
Should we?
We need to dip our feet in the water while we're here.
(Let's deep our feet in the water as we've come to the beach.)
- Why are there no people?
- Yes. It's empty.
It's beautiful.
- The water comes up this far.
- Yes.
(Jung Ah walks across the white sand toward the sea.)
It's cold.
How's the water? Is it cold or not?
- It's very cold.
- She said it's very cold.
(A picturesque solo shot)
You look pretty, Jung Ah.
- Yes?
- You look pretty. Run for me.
- Run?
- Yes.
(Dashing)
No, Jung Ah. Not like that.
(When she is told to run,)
(she sprints at full speed.)
- Jung Ah!
- Jung Ah, jump.
No, Jung Ah. Run prettily with some style.
No? Didn't you ask her to jump?
Do you want me to hop?
No. Just run while looking graceful.
(Running gracefully)
(Scratching)
("Jung Ah is not here.")
(Running in a dorky way)
Jung Ah.
(She can't believe her.)
You can pull off slapstick now.
(Just hurry and come.)
It's hilarious.
How can she be so funny just by running?
(Following Jung Ah, they walk across the sandy beach.)
(Running)
- Isn't it cold? Are you okay?
- I'm good.
(The eldest is worried as the sea breeze is still cold.)
- Gosh. This place...
- It's so vast.
It feels too precious to walk over it.
It's like walking on the first snow.
How can it be this pretty? It's so clean.
Gosh. This is like...
- the beach in an Italian film.
- It's beautiful.
The beach I've never been to.
(Up close, it looks like the beach in an Italian film.)
- Gosh. I love it.
- Do you like it?
(It feels even better...)
(because they're here together at this beautiful place.)
- Gosh. They look fabulous.
- "How have you been?"
The two are looking great.
Don't they look like a couple...
- who have come to break up?
- A breakup trip?
- A breakup trip.
Why do they break up?
It feels that way because of the colours.
(Amazed)
- The guy doesn't want to break up.
- I see.
But he has to.
- Right. He trudges along behind.
- Yes.
- And the view...
- It's so pretty.
Yes, it's so pretty.
(Do we really have to end it?)
Doesn't this place have a soulful vibe?
It's a bit...
It's a bit gloomy.
Right. I'm wearing sunglasses.
I wondered why it was so dark.
Why? What is it this time?
(What is going on again?)
- Hold on.
- I thought it felt gloomy...
for some reason.
These were why. And I thought,
(The sea is blue and so clear.)
(But for Sun Young, it was hazy and muted.)
"Gosh. This sea is so gloomy."
It was because of these.
- Let me try them on to see it.
- That was why I said...
the sea is gloomy like the one in an Italian film.
- Yes, Sun Young.
- That was it.
It feels like a non-digital film.
- Yes. Exactly.
- They mute the colours.
- They have a yellow filter.
- I can't believe myself.
(It looks like an old movie.)
- Everyone, I was wrong. It's...
- Sun Young.
(Embarrassed)
It's a clear, beautiful sea.
For goodness' sake. I thought they were breaking up.
I don't need them.
(You Seok dips his feet in the water.)
The water is cold, indeed.
(Yoon Seo dips her feet like You Seok.)
- It's nice and cold, Jung Ah.
- The water is cold.
(She walks right in while saying it's cold.)
It feels nice.
Gosh. We're at the sea!
(We need to enjoy the sea even though the water is cold.)
(At the beach, you have to play in the water.)
(Attacking Yoon Seo right away)
(She never goes easy on him just because he's older.)
(She grabs a floating piece of seaweed...)
(and surprises You Seok.)
You scared me.
(Laughing)
- Let's jump on 3.
- We'll jump on 3.
Jung Ah, we'll jump on three.
(These two are like our parents.)
- One, two, three.
- No!
(At the beach in Taean)
- Gosh. It's so pretty.
- Great.
Look at them.
Gosh. Fresh off the Sea.
(Leaving their mark on the beach before they leave)
- The letter suddenly got bigger.
- I know.
The first letter was too small.
(You Seok writes "Fresh.")
(And Yoon Seo writes "Off the Sea" below it.)
- Where should I put this?
- Between these letters.
(And the local specialties they can't leave out)
(We were here in Taean. Fresh off the Sea.)
- Bye.
(The siblings made new memories in Taean.)
(The siblings' third story, Hadong)
(Hiding beneath the winding Seomjin River...)
(are countless treasures.)
(Catch the marsh clams!)
(Welcome. Isn't it your first time working in the river?)
(But it's harder...)
(than they expected.)
(They work with a 15-kg pet georaengi.)
(The most gruelling labour)
(It’s almost a form of penance.)
(Suddenly,)
(the water gets deeper.)
(What will happen to the siblings in the Seomjin River?)
(And an insane menu lineup is on standby!)
(Made with freshly caught marsh clams)
(is the new type of clam chowder with marsh clams.)
(And Chef Yum's first kkakdugi in large quantity)
(You Seok is the head chef this time.)
(Crispy pork cutlet made by Chef Kang)
(The siblings' joyful dinner is coming soon!)